SHANI PATEL

SOFTWARE QUALITY ASSURANCE ENGINEER

+91 8238358272 patelshani9044@gmail.com

Summary

Software Quality Assurance Engineer with experience in all levels of testing, including performance, functional, integration, system, regression, and user acceptance testing. Supportive and enthusiastic team player dedicated to streamlining processes and efficiently resolving project issues.

Skill Highlights

- Agile/Scrum methodology
- **Firebase**

- Trello
- Postman

Experience

Junior Software Quality Assurance Engineer- June 2021 to July 2022 Vasundhara Infotech, Surat, Gujarat

- Good Knowledge on Software Development Life Cycle and Software Test Life Cycle.
- Knowledge on Various SDLC Models, Test Levels, Test Types and test Design Techniques.
- Knowledge on Generating Test Scenarios, Write Test Cases, and collect Test Data.
- Knowledge on Executing Test Batches and Analyzing Test Result.
- Knowledge on Defect Reporting, Defect Tracking and complete Defect Life cycle.
- Knowledge on Writing & Executing SQL Statements.
- Good interpersonal skills, committed, result oriented, hard working to Learn technologies.

Software Quality Assurance Engineer - July 2022 to Present Key Concepts, Surat, Gujarat

- Collaborated with developers and product owners to stay current on product features and intended functionality.
- Proposed development and testing improvements to positively impact usability, function and performance.
- Wrote and optimized test cases to maximize success of manual software testing with consistent, thorough approaches

Education

Bachelor Of Engineer: Electrical Engineer - Sept 2020

L.D College Of Engineering

Diploma Engineering: Electrical Engineer – June 2017

DR S & S.S Ghandhy College 10TH G.S.H.S.E.B - May 2014 J.B Vidhyalaya Gothava.

Responsibilities

- Understanding and analyzing Software Requirements.
- Follow testing guidelines.
- Execute test cases according to plan.
- Conduct testing.
- Record test results.
- Report errors according to procedures.

Certificate

Software testing Course from Tops Technology. Hands on experience of Web Testing and MOBILE application Testing. **Feb 2021 – Jun 2021**

Personal Details

• Name: Shanikumar Rajanikant Patel

• D.O.B: 04 July 1999

• Language Known: English, Hindi, Gujarati

Marital Status: SingleNationality: Indian.

Declaration

• I hear by declare that the above mentioned information is true to the best of my knowledge.

Your Sincerely

Shani Patel.